<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>n00bmind&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on n00bmind&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal projects</title>
      <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/projects/</guid>
      <description>dodo-lang A sandbox to explore language design ideas while I learn more about compilers. I had written my own scripting language before, but never a &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; language, and never writing all the code myself from scratch. At the moment it&amp;rsquo;s just barely a transpiler to C, but I hope to continue adding code generation and maybe even explore some optimization techniques.robotrider An engine/game still in very early development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional experience</title>
      <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 08:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/experience/</guid>
      <description>Engine programmer @ Glowmade Nov 2019 - present Worked on new unnanounced titles
Working in a small studio creating new features for their proprietary engine, both low level and user level, including &amp;ldquo;tyding up&amp;rdquo; the memory usage across the entire engine and game and adding runtime statistics, creating a prefab subsystem from scratch for use with their entity system, a few user-level editor tools, some improvements in the content packaging and general resource system, working on portability across platforms, integrating external profiling tools, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 18:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
I&amp;rsquo;m Oscar Peñas. I was born a loong time ago somewhere in the south coast of Spain. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in computers almost since I can remember, ever since I got my amazing 8086 as a birthday present I felt so very curious about how it did what it did.
However it was when I first discovered the demoscene, in the mid 90s, that I really was hooked forever. I had to learn how to do all that!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
