<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>n00bmind&#39;s Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on n00bmind&#39;s Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
I&amp;rsquo;m Oscar Peñas. I was born a loong time ago somewhere in the south coast of Spain. I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in computers almost since I can remember, ever since I got my amazing 8086 for my 9th birthday I felt so incredibly curious about how it did what it did. At first it was mostly just playing games and tinkering with MS-DOS, then one day I started learning some QBasic and a whole world opened before my eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal projects</title>
      <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/projects/</guid>
      <description>dodo-lang A sandbox to explore language design ideas while I learn more about compilers. I had written my own scripting language before, but never a &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; language, and never writing all the code myself from scratch. At the moment it&amp;rsquo;s just barely a transpiler to C, but I hope to continue adding code generation and maybe even explore some optimization techniques.    robotrider An engine/game still in very early development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional experience</title>
      <link>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://portfolio.n00bmind.me/experience/</guid>
      <description>Engine programmer @ Glowmade 2023 - present (as Principal engine programmer) Nov 2019 - 2023 Titles: Rustheart (cancelled), Unnanounced
Working in a small-ish studio implementing many new features for their proprietary engine, both low level and user level, including: &amp;ldquo;tyding up&amp;rdquo; and improving the various memory subsystems across the entire engine and game and adding runtime memory statistics and tooling, many low-level threading improvements, creating a prefab subsystem from scratch for use by content creators together with the entity system, a few user-level editor tools, some improvements in the content packaging and general resource system, working on a generic platform layer for portability across platforms, integrating external profiling tools, continued performance investigations etc etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
